这是什么？ 咯咯叫的虫子
So,what is this?Googlie Worm.
这个呢？ 毛毛球
And this?Glow Pop Jiggly Jam.
好好玩喔
It's so funny!
这是什么？
What's this?
去年剩的一块三明治
A hunk of sandwich from last year.
盖勒钓到了！看来是条大鱼
Geller's got one hooked! Looks like a big one!
经典的人鱼大战…
It's the classic struggle between man
有人撞倒一盏台灯
Someone knocked over a lamp.
你们知道去钓鱼最棒的是什么吗？
You know what'll be great about the fishing trip?
到了湖中央 爸会问我“你都在忙什么”
When my Dad asks,"What are you doing with your life?"...
我可以说
...I can say,
我要跟查尔顿・赫斯顿（电影演员）演电影 你呢？
"I'm doing a movie with Charlton Heston.What about you?"
别因为我出来就不笑了 凯西没有背叛你们
Don't stop having fun just because I'm here.Kathy didn't cheat on all of you.
当然，也背叛了你
Well,except you.
最感人的是 那两只鸡鸭一直跟着他
You know what is so sweet? Those birds have not left his side the whole time.
那只公鸡怎么不死
Yeah,I wish that rooster were dead.
乔伊，你不该丢下钱德 他跟凯西才分手2天
You shouldn't leave Chandler alone. They broke up only two days ago.
下周再去钓鱼吧
Go fishing next week.
我帮不上忙，他还穿着运动裤
There's nothing I can do. He's still in his sweats.
现在才第一阶段
That's only phase one.
我第二阶段会回来 我从不错过第二阶段
I'll be back for phase two. I'd never miss that.
什么第二阶段？
Phase two?
喝个烂醉，上脱衣舞厅
Getting drunk and going to a strip club.
那样怎么会有帮助？ 那里有裸女
How does going there make him better?There are naked ladies there.
然后就是第三阶段 对别的女人产生性幻想
Then to phase three: seeing yourself with other women.
那个阶段也有裸女
There are naked ladies there too.
让我清静一下好吗？
Would you give me one minute,please?
本集播出：“乔伊肮脏的一天”
The One with Joey's Dirty Day
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
这跟你上星期挑的外套配？
These will match the jacket you picked out last week?
这就对了…就是这样…
There we go.There it is.
你知道我需要什么？手套
You know what I need? Gloves.
棕色的皮手套
Brown leather dress gloves.
好，我看看，这只手是大号
Well,let's see....This one is large.
这只手… 也是大号？
And this one....Also large?
对，两只大号的手套马上来
Two larges coming right up.
瑞秋，耽误你一下 好
-Damn you. -Could I have a moment?
我的侄女从伦敦来玩
My niece,you see,is in town from London.
其实是什罗普郡
Shropshire,but you know.
她跟你差不多大
She's about your age,I'd say.
总之我有两张歌剧的票
Anyway,I have tickets for the opera.
“蝙蝠”（著名轻歌剧） 你今晚愿意陪她吗？
Die Fledermaus.Would you like to keep her company tonight?
好，没问题 太好了，算我一份
Sure. You got it!
我和“蝙蝠”，太棒了
Count me in. Me. Fledermaus. Great!
好，谢谢，谢谢，谢谢你
Yes,of course. Thank you so very much.
所以…？
So?
怎样？
So what？
手套？ 对喔，我马上去拿
-Gloves? -Sorry,I'll be right back.
其实我该走了
Actually,I got to take off.
不晓得你今晚有没有事？ 没有，没事
I was curious. Do you have plans tonight?No,nothing!
我投资的夜总会今晚开幕 你要去吗？
I invested in a nightclub. It opens tonight. Want to come?
好啊，太棒了
That would be great!
你喜欢性虐待的主题吧？
You're into hard-core S & M,right?
应该… 开玩笑的
-Well,I guess. -I'm kidding.
我会先到，我会把你列为贵宾 进来找我
I'll put you on the VlP list. Look for me.
好，没问题
Great! You bet.
晚上见 好
I'll see you tonight.
差点忘了给你票 什么？
-I almost forgot the tickets. -What?
你和艾蜜莉，今晚 “蝙蝠”
For you and Emily. Tonight. Die Fledermaus.
对喔
Oh,right.
你一定会喜欢 三大男高音（帕瓦罗蒂、卡雷拉斯、多明戈）去了两个
You'll like it. It has two out of the three tenors.
凯西居然这样对我 我真的以为我要定下来了
I can't believe Kathy did this to me.I really thought she was the one.
告诉你们 我再也不离开这张椅子了
I'll tell you what.I'm not getting out of this chair. Ever!
以后我要定在这张椅子上
From now on,this chair is the one!
还有这条运动裤
You know what else is the one? My sweatpants.
别这样，把运动裤脱掉
Just take the sweats off,okay?
脱掉，我们来玩
Take them off and we'll have some fun.
我抗拒不了这个诱惑 所以我都不穿运动裤
Wow,and I can't resist that line. That's why I never wear sweatpants.
有钓到大鱼吗？ 说出来吓死你们
Did you catch any fish?You guys have no idea.
你好臭 搞什么
-You stink! -Are you kidding?
我3天没洗澡 还掉进一桶鱼饵里
Three days without a shower. Plus,I fell in a big tub of worms!
他怎么样？ 2天没离开那张椅子
How's he doing?He hasn't left that chair in two days.
兄弟，你还好吗？
Hey,buddy,how's it going?
好兄弟回家就没事了
You see? He just needed his pal to come home.
我得背台词
I got to memorize my lines.
明天一早 要和查尔顿・赫斯顿演戏
Me and Charlton Heston,bright and early tomorrow,baby!
莫妮卡 怎么了？
Hi，monica。-What's the matter?
约书亚约我参加夜总会开幕
Joshua invited me to this fancy club opening tonight.
但我已经答应沃森先生 要带他的侄女去看老掉牙歌剧
But I already told Mr. Waltham...that I would take his niece to the dumb old opera.
能怎么办呢？
So,what are you going to do?
我不知道 不行，救救我
-I don't know. -No! Help me!
我不行，我要工作 菲比？
-I can't. I have to work. -Phoebe?
我很想，但我都在晚上害喜
I would,but I get my morning sickness in the evening.
除非她想整晚帮我捞住头发
Unless she wants to spend the night holding my hair back for me.
拜托啦，我一定要去找约书亚
You guys,come on! I have to meet Joshua.
这样他才能看到有趣的瑞秋
It's my one chance for him to see the "fun" Rachel.
“娶来当老婆会很棒”的瑞秋
The "wouldn't it be great if she were my wife?" Rachel.
乔伊和钱德回来了吗？
Are Joey and Chandler back?
钱德还在第一阶段 乔伊就是臭味的来源
Chandler's still in phase one,and Joey's that thing you smell.
所以…？
So....
不要
No.
拜托啦
Come on!
应该是她 等一下，罗斯，拜托啦
-She's here. -Wait,wait.Ross,please?
你要我带一个不认识的女生 去看歌剧
You want me to take some girl I've never met to the opera...
好让你去夜总会 跟某个男人打情骂俏？
...so you can go to a club and flirt with some guy?
真难决定啊
That is a toughie.
她在看走廊
She's looking down the hall.
她在看我
She looked right at me.
这样看是看不到的，对吧？
You can't see people through that hole,can you?
马上来
I'll be right there! Okay,Ross,please.
罗斯，拜托啦 我以为我们已经放得开了
I thought we had moved on.
我以为我们可以彼此祝福了 难道只有我是？
I thought we could be happy for each other.I mean,was that just me?
好吧 谢谢你，谢谢
All right,I'll do it.Thank you,thank you.
艾蜜莉
Emily？
是 我是瑞秋格林
Yes. I'm Rachel Greene.
谢天谢地
Thank goodness!
计划有小小的变动 我晚上没空，所以…
There's been a teeny change of plans. I'm not free tonight
是吗？
Really?
太好了，我一定是没接到电话 虽然我整天都没出门
I must've missed your call,though I didn't leave the flat all day.
我… 不，这也没什么
Well,l
我来到这里 先是被你们的热狗车撞倒
That's not rude. It's in keeping with the trip...where I've been run down by one of your wiener carts
在机场又被脱衣服搜身
...and been strip-searched at the airport.
显然我长得就像 屁股里塞了可卡因
Apparently,I look like someone who's got cocaine stuffed up their bum.
我觉得你很漂亮啊
I think you look great.
再见，很高兴认识你
Good night. It was very nice to meet you.
我去追她
I'll get her.
快去 好
Please,hurry.
他们讲话好好玩
Don't you just love the way they talk?
怎么了？ 宝宝在踢
-What? -The baby kicked!Oh,my God.
不对，是内裤的松紧带断了
No,wait. The elastic in my underwear busted.
完了，我睡过头了
Oh,my God! I overslept!
通告是半小时前，我得赶快
I was supposed to be on the set half an hour ago!
你不能这样去，你好臭
You can't go like that! You stink!
我睡着忘记洗澡 现在没时间了
I fell asleep. Now I don't have time!
才十条街，用跑的还来得及
Just 10 blocks away. If I run,I'll make it.
跑十条街会更臭
Run 10 blocks. That'll help the smell.
慢一点！不，你走吧
Slow down! No,keep moving.
昨晚怎么样啊？
How did it go last night?
我没见到约书亚 但我揍了一个女生一拳
Well,I didn't see Joshua.But I did punch a girl in the face.
什么？ 为什么？
What?Why?
昨晚真的很倒霉，雨下得很大
The whole night was horrible. It was pouring.
到了现场名单上没有瑞秋格林 但有一个瑞秋葛皮
There was no Rachel Greene on the list. But there was a Rachel Greep.
你有见到她吗？
So did you get to meet her?
根本没这个人 但有个女生听到了
There is no Rachel Greep. But this girl overheard us.
大叫“我就是瑞秋葛皮” 结果她就进去了
And she said,"I'm Rachel Greep!" And he let her in.
所以你揍她？
So you hit her?
不是，她已经进去了 不过后面有个肥婆想偷我的伞
No,she was already in.This big bitch behind me tried to steal my umbrella
我扁了她
...so I clocked her.
真是的，我只想在工作之余 跟约书亚相处一下
All I wanted was a few hours...outside of work to see Joshua
好让他有机会爱上我
...so he could go ahead and start falling in love with me.
菲
Pheebs.
亲爱的，那是你的名字
Honey,that's your name.
那是“菲比”的缩写吗？我还以为那是我们之间的匿称
That's short for Phoebe? I thought that's what we called each other.
你穿上裤子了 没错
-You're wearing pants! -That's right.
男生呢？我要买醉看脱衣舞了
Where are the guys? I'm ready to get drunk and see strippers.
才早上9点半 那里有早餐自助餐
It's 9:30 a.m.They got a breakfast buffet.
喂…罗斯
Hello!Oh,hey, Ross
让我跟他说
Let me talk to him!
天哪 我能不能…
-Oh,my God! -Can't I just?
什么？ 我的电话她还嘘我
-It's my phone and she's shush -Please!
别吵啦！他说什么？
What's he saying?
他跟艾蜜莉在佛罗蒙特投宿 什么？天哪
He's with Emily in Vermont.What? Oh,my God!
艾蜜莉是谁？不！
Who the hell is Emily? No.
刚见面的时候 她从头到脚都湿透了
When we first met her,she was soaking,her feet were wet....
任谁都会心情不好
Who wouldn't be miserable?
我一让她换上干的鞋子 她就完全变了
I'm telling you,once l got her into a dry pair of shoes...she was a totally different person.
他们在佛罗蒙特？怎么会？
They're in Vermont? How did this happen?
他怎么会跟那个巫婆去佛罗蒙特
How'd he end up in Vermont with that witch?
也许她没有一直打他吧
Maybe she doesn't hit him all the time.
罗斯，快来 外面有只驯鹿在吃果园的水果
There's a deer outside eating fruit from the orchard!
我要挂了 外面有只驯鹿在吃果园的水果
I got to go! There's a deer eating fruit from the orchard!
他挂了 外面有只驯鹿在吃果园的水果
He had to go. There was a deer eating fruit from the orchard.
我不懂，她很恐怖
I don't get this. She was horrible!
我要去站在那边
I'm going to go stand over there.
你干嘛这么在乎？ 我才不在乎
Why do you care?I don't care.
我只是很气我跟约书亚没进展
I'm just upset that I'm getting nowhere with Joshua.
但哪有人一认识 就跑去佛罗蒙特的
You do not just meet someone and go flitting off to Vermont!
你和贝瑞一认识就跑去维尔鬼混
When you first met Barry,you flitted off to Vail.
你能不能偶尔有一次 不要什么小事都记得
Could you,just for once...not remember every little thing?
他什么时候回来？ 过两天吧
So you know,when's he getting back?A couple of days.
我就知道会这样
I knew something like this would happen.
你干什么？
What are you doing?
钱德，你不能让阶段倒流
You can't go back a phase!
可以，时间才不能倒流
You're thinking about time. You can't go back in time.
我们跟你去进行第二阶段好了
Why don't you do your phase two strip club thing with us?
对呀，我们可以当男生
We can be guys!
你们不行
No,you can't.
让我们当嘛，也许我们想当
Let us be guys! Maybe we want to be guys.
你们才不想，全身是毛还短命
No,you don't. You'd be all hairy and wouldn't live as long.
别这么孬种
Would you just stop being such a wuss
把运动裤脱掉 跟我们去看裸女跳舞
and get those off?And come with us and watch naked girls dance!
好
Okay.
对不起
I'm sorry.
银杯片厂（纽约最大的电影和电视制作中心）
我是乔伊崔比亚尼，我来了
Joey Tribbiani. I'm here.
别急，来得及，进度有点落后
Calm down,we got time. We're running late.All set.
你看，查尔顿・赫斯顿在嚼甘草
Look at that. Charlton Heston eating licorice.
他很爱嚼甘草，老是…
Yeah,he loves them. I've never seen him with
搞什么？
What the hell is that?
什么东西这么臭？ 你
What smells so bad?You.
难怪你会这么想，不过…
I could see why you would think that. But
你知道其实是谁？ 你？
you know who it is?You?
不，是赫斯顿
No,no. It's Heston.
什么？
What?
他臭得好像去钓了3天鱼 现在还嚼甘草
He reeks like he went on a three-day fishing trip,then ate licorice.
不可能 只有他的休息室有浴室
No way. He's the only one with a shower in his dressing room.
真的？浴室？
Really? A shower?
是哪一间？ 门口有写“赫斯顿”的那间
Which room might that be?The one with "Heston" on it.
有意思
Interesting.
我换了零钞 你要不要去塞她的小裤裤？
I got some ones. You want to put them in her panties?
不用了，妈
No,thanks,Mom!
抱歉，你得熄掉，我怀孕了
That.You have to put that out because I'm pregnant.
也许你和你的孩子应该去别家
Maybe you and your baby ought to go to another strip club.
这才不是我的孩子
It's not my baby.
很好
Very good.
太棒了，我喜欢，很火辣
Really good. I enjoyed it. Very exotic.
我查过留言，约书亚没打来
I just checked our messages and Joshua didn't call.
我还以为我没去他会担心
You'd think he'd be worried about me not showing up.
更糟的是 罗斯正在佛罗蒙特风流快活
You know what makes it worse?Ross is all happy in Vermont.
拜托，你在看脱衣舞耶
Come on,look where you are!
麻烦你给我们每人一杯鸡尾酒 记得我要纯的
Another round of daiquiris.Virgin for me.
走之前别忘了告诉我地毯旁边那个帅哥的名字
Don't let me leave without the name of that carpet guy.
凯伦，还有，你最好…
Cherry,you know,you…
拜托！
Come on!
算了，我要回家打给凯西
You know what? I'll go home and call Kathy.
如果有用的话 不，那是个考验
If it'll help.That was a test.
再过几小时我会喝醉想打给她 你们得阻止我
In a few hours,I'll be drunk.I'll want to call her. You'll have to stop me.
接着我会烂醉到想打给珍妮丝
Then I'll be so drunk,I'll want to call Janice.
你是该打，她好吗？
You should! How is she?
有人需要再来一次腿舞喔
I think somebody needs another lap dance.
谁在里面？
Who's in there?
你好吗？ 你是谁？
How you doing?Who in the hell are you?
如果我说我是科克道格拉斯（著名演员）你不会信吧？
Would you believe me if I said I was Kirk Douglas?
把裤子穿上，我好踹你的屁股
Put some pants on,kid,so I can kick your butt.
不，等等，你有所不知
No,wait. You don't understand.
我是个演员
I'm an actor.
乔伊崔比亚尼 今天跟你有一场戏
Joey Tribbiani. I'm doing a scene with you today.
但是我很臭（演得很烂）
And I stink!
你有演这部片？
You're in this picture?
对，我演不肯跟你合作的警察 因为你很我行我素
I'm a cop who won't work with you because you're a loose cannon.
总之我很抱歉 但我真的很臭（演得很烂）
Anyway,I'm really sorry.But I stink.
乔伊是吧？ 对
Joey,right?
每个演员或多或少…
Every actor,one time or another
都会觉得自己烂
Every actor thinks he stinks.
连劳伦斯奥立佛（演技卓越的大师） 有时也会这么想
Even Laurence Olivier sometimes thought he stank.
鲍勃雷德福德（演员、导演、制片人）根本不看自己演戏
Bob Redford won't even watch himself.
不，你没听懂
You don't understand.
听我说 是
Listen to me.
每一个好演员
I don't know one actor worth his salt...
在演艺生涯中都曾说过 “天哪，我真烂”
...who,one time in his career,didn't say,"God,I stink!"
我刚拍完一场戏 第一次我演得烂透了
I just did a scene out there. First take,I stunk the place up.
重要的是你要记住 不管你认为自己有多烂
The important thing,and you must remember...no matter how badly you think you stink
也不能闯进我的休息室 用我的浴室
...you must never,ever bust into my dressing room and use my shower!
懂了吗？ 是，很抱歉
Do you understand me?Yes,sir. I'm very sorry.
等等，把裤子带走 是
Wait a minute!Take your pants.
对不起，很抱歉
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
演艺圈
What a business.
我们表现得还好吧？ 好得很
We did okay at the strip club,right?Great.
你们让最性感的服务生 要辞职去当三年级的老师
Thanks to you,the hottest waitress is quitting to teach the third grade!
他居然还没打来
-He still hasn't called.
约许吗？ 是约书亚
-Who,Josh?It's Joshua.
他不喜欢约许？ 是我不喜欢
-He doesn't like "Josh"? -No,I don't.
我要把运动裤换回来
I'm going to put my sweats back on.
不要啦！你说得对
You know what? You were right.
我们当男生当得不好 你知道为什么？
We weren't great at being guys. You know why?
因为我们是女生
Because we're girls.
你知道女生最擅长什么？ 跳脱衣舞
-You know what girls are good at? -Stripping!
不，是倾听，坐下
No,listening!Sit.
如果你肯一吐为快 或许就没事了
Maybe it would really,really help if you would just talk.
是啊，你的心在想什么？
Yeah,come on. What's going on in there?
你想哭也没关系
And you know,if you want to cry,that's okay too.
我要请你们都离开
I'm going to have to ask you all to leave.
别这样嘛 钱德
Come on. Chandle
算了，我们试过了 但第三阶段没希望了
Forget it. We tried,but phase three is a lost cause.
那些舞娘都很辣 我却无法产生性幻想
Those strippers were hot,and l couldn't picture myself with them.
她们真的很漂亮
They really were pretty,weren't they?
我喜欢一号战斗机驾驶
-I liked that fighter pilot one. -Candy?
糖糖？她好有劲 对啊
She was so spunky!
要是我要跟女人在一起…
I think if I were going to be with a woman...
我会选蜜雪儿那型的 她好娇小
...it'd be with someone like Michelle.She was just so petite.
我会选香妲
For me,it would have to be Chantal.
她的皮肤好嫩，我塞钱给她时
She had the smoothest skin.I stuck that dollar in her G-string
手擦过她的大腿… 第三阶段！
and grazed her thigh. Phase three!
我进入第三阶段了
I just achieved phase three!
真的？ 我可以想像你们跟她们在一起
I am totally picturing you with all those women!
那不是第三阶段 我也在场
That's not phase three.Well,I'm there too!
我们在开性派对吗？ 别说了，我快疯了
Are we all together in a group?Stop it,you're killing me!
我进入第四阶段了 那是什么？
I think I moved on to phase four!What is that?
我再也不想谈恋爱 只想跟脱衣舞娘和朋友上床
I don't want a relationship ever!I just want sex with strippers and my friends!
来嘛，让我看看你的笑容
Come on.Let me see that smile.
我不想笑 拜托啦？
I don't want to.Please?
我想看脱衣舞嘛
I wanted to go to the strip club!
你有的是机会 有成千上万的女人等着伤害我
You'll have plenty of chances.There are thousands of women out there,just waiting to screw me over.
好吧
Yeah,all right.
佛罗蒙特怎样？
How was Vermont?
艾蜜莉真是…太棒了 她好得无法形容
Emily is...incredible. There are no words to describe her.
整个周末就像一场梦
The whole weekend was like a dream.
还有你，瑞秋
And you! Rach!
你说得一点也没错 什么？
You were so right.What?
你说我们总算到了一个 可以彼此祝福的阶段
What you said about us finally being in a place where we could really be happy for each other.
我原本没那么放得开 想到你和那个约许…
I admit,I wasn't quite there.The thought of you and that Josh guy
约书亚 约书亚，在俱乐部里跳舞狂欢
Joshua.Joshua guy at that club,dancing,having a good time
我就觉得… 你懂吗？但现在…
And the thought of it kind of....You know? But now!
我完全放开了 我终于跟你一样了
But now,I'm totally there.I'm finally where you are.
谢天谢地
Thank goodness!
谢谢你把艾蜜莉介绍给我
And thank you for Emily.
不客气，我乐得帮忙 我很替你开心
No problem. I'm so glad I could help,you know?I'm happy for you.
我才替你开心
Happy for you.
不，我才替你开心
Oh,no,happy for you.
好，接下来是这样
All right. Here's what we'll do.
你帮我脱衣服
You are going to take off my clothes.
你们两个去拿精油
You two,go get the oils.
你就一直兴奋的叫 “钱德是国王！钱德是国王”
And you,just constantly scream..."Chandler's the king! Chandler's the king!"
我想跟她在一起，我喜欢她
I want to be with her. I like her.
没问题，大家随意
That's fine. Go with your instincts!
我要做什么？
What am I doing again?
专心一点，我随时都会醒来
Pay attention. I could wake up at any moment.
我是约书亚，我来接瑞秋
I'm Joshua. I'm here to pick up Rachel.
他不是约书亚
That's not Joshua.
你想怎样？我又没见过他
What do you want from me? I never met the guy.
可惜你要走了 我们还有很多事要忙
I'm sorry you can't stay.The rest of us have a lot of work to do.
你干什么？
What are you doing?
好，我得醒过来
All right,listen. I got to wake up.